Metal Cardbot Commentary!
The Unlicensed Doctor, Mega Ambler
Hey guys! Jun again!
Let's watch another episode of Metal Cardbot together!
It's "Metal Cardbot Commentary" time!
Mega Ambler, setup!
My name is Mega Ambler.
I am a doctor who took care of many patients back on planet Machina.
It's nice to see you, Mega Ambler!
Today, let's see the story of how I met Mega Ambler.
Shall we get started?
The black ambulance?
That's right. An ambulance blackened by soot.
The children taken away as its prey will have their souls stolen by the Grim Reaper,
never to be seen again.
Aah!! I'm so scared!
Is that what you wanted to hear? Then you'll need to try a better story!
Y-yeah, we know it's just a myth!
I've heard about it too.
A child was kidnapped by the black ambulance, and by the time he was found...
he had been turned into a mummy!
Aah!
Stop it already, Anna!
So there were rumors about me going around like that...
Mega Ambler!
What on earth were you trying to do to those kids?
I only took the injured children to bandage them up.
Huh?
You wrapped them up way too much!
I'm back!
Hey Jun, what's up?
What's going on?
I'm giving them a health checkup.
Ah, a health checkup...
Is Edo knowledgeable in that field?
Mega Ambler!
How about you try joining them next time?
No.
If you keep running like those two, your health will decline.
Ahaha... I guess things got a little heated.
Blue Cop is in tip-top shape.
I do feel better than ever.
Mega Trucker, you have a worn out damper in your knee.
Wait, what?
How can you tell?
Because, after ten years in this job, I can tell a lot just by the sound of things.
Whaddya mean? I need fixing? No way!
Uncle Edo's the best mechanic around. You can count on him, even if he is a bit of a grump.
Hey, I heard that.
Jun...
Now, let me have a look at you.
Look... at me...?
Lie down and stay still.
Hm. No broken bones.
Alright, then.
Examination complete.
Wrapping things up.
What is going on?
Help me, Jun!
I told you to stay still!
Theo! Are you okay?!
Jun...
I don't think there was any need to break down the door like that.
I... I was in a hurry to come and save Theo!
Hmm...
As a doctor, I only wanted to sufficiently treat him.
It looked more like you were trying to dress him up like a mummy...?
Are there more robots?
Who are you, then?
You don't know each other?
Mega Ambler is a notorious travelling doctor.
He goes around treating people without a license,
and charging them exorbitant fees.
But you can't deny my skills are the real deal!
Blue Cop!
Broke out of your bandages, I see.
It's no use trying to find a weak spot.
I take thorough care of myself. Unlike a certain someone...
I heard that!
Maybe so.
But a weak spot can easily be made!
That's not what a doctor does!
Blue Cop, Burst Shot!
Burst... Shot!
Forceps Shock!
What's wrong? Should I have a look?
That didn't even leave a scratch.
Huh...?
That's not good.
Aah! What's wrong with your arm?!
I'll take care of your other arm too!
Blue Cop, watch out!
I am always serious and reserved.
How could I fall over so ridiculously...?
It's because my joint strategy with Blue Cop worked!
Huh?
Blue Cop, I was embarrassed enough already.
But you swung it without even thinking?
Ah... That's not it! It was all part of my plan!
Well.
I'll admit the last attack was definitely well thought out.
I'll make it so you can't move at all!
Now! Megabolt Punch!
Mega...bolt...
Punch!!
Well, everyone?
I was able to rescue Theo safely,
and I also sealed Mega Ambler!
I hope you'll all look forward to the next "Metal Cardbot Commentary"!